Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- American Labor Conference on International Affairs. Labor's stake in Bretton Woods, 1945; Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Labor's Stake in Bretton Woods, Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
    By Broadus Mitchell and Francis L. Hauser of the Research Department of the I. L. G. W. U. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- American Paper and Pulp Association. New Horizons:, 1952; Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: New Horizons - A History of Seventy-Five Years of the American Paper and Pulp Association, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
    By American Paper and Pulp Association. Informational Booklet - February 21, 1952. Item is in English.
- Armour and Company. Progress report, Automation Committee, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Progress Report Automotion Committee, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
    By Amrmour and Company. September 1, 1959. Item is in English.
- Best Foods. Best Foods employee handbook, 1990; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    By Best Foods. June 1, 1990. Item is in English.
- Bituminous Operators' Special Committee. Campaign of the United Mine Workers of America, 1923; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Brief No. 6 Utah, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
    By Bituminous Operators' Special Committee. June 28, 1923. Item is in English.
- Black Workers' Freedom Convention. Black workers take the lead!, 1972; Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Black Workers Take The Lead!, Publication (Box 34, Folder 13)
    By Black Workers' Freedom Convention. September 2nd & 3rd 1972 -. Item is in English.
- Brown University. Manpower revolution/Brown University Associates, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Revolution, Publication (Box 34, Folder 14)
    By Brown University. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Bureau of National Affairs. Where you stand under the Labor Reform Law: Labor-Management Reform Law of 1959, Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Where You Stand Under The Labor Reform Law, Publication (Box 34, Folder 15)
    By Bureau of National Affairs. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- California. Commission on Manpower, Automation and Technology. Report to the Governor and the Legislature/Commission on Manpower, Automation and Technology, State of California, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Report to the Governor and the Legislature, Publication (Box 34, Folder 16)
    By California. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- California. Industrial Welfare Commission. Budget for a self-supporting Working Woman, 1961; Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Budget for a Self-Supporting Working Woman, Publication (Box 34, Folder 17)
    By California Industrial Welfare Commission. June 1961 - Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Chamber of Commerce of the United States. Case for voluntary unionism: a discussion of the merits of 'right to work' laws and the dangers of compulsory unionism, 1955; Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Case for Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 34, Folder 18)
    By Chamber of Commerce of the United States. March 1957. Item is in English.
- Chicago Typothetae. Emergency Committee. Final report of the Emergency Committee of the Chicago Typothetae: on the strike of Chicago Typographical Union No. 16: with an appendix, 1888; Publication (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Final Report of the Emergency Committee, Publication (Box 34, Folder 19)
    By Chicago Thypothetae. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Citizens Committee to Free Earl Browder, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Comparative Study of the Earl Browder and other Passport Cases, Publication (Box 34, Folder 20)
    By Citizens' Committee to Free Earl Browder. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Citizens Joint Commission of Inquiry Report of Citizens Joint, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Report of Citizens Joint Commission of Inquiry on South Chicago Memorial Day Incident, Publication (Box 34, Folder 21)
    By Citizens Joint Commission of Inquiry. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. Committee on Labor Relations. Labor relations in Cleveland: a declaration of principles, 1920; Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations in Cleveland, Publication (Box 34, Folder 22)
    By The Cleveland Chamber of Commerce. April 7, 1920. Item is in English.
- Coalition of Labor Union Women. Union women speak out on health issues including abortion: Results of a survey of the CLUW chapters, 1993; Publication (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Union Women Speak Out on Health Issues including abortion, Publication (Box 34, Folder 23)
    By Coalition of Labor Union Women Center for Education & Research Reproductive Right Project. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Coalition of Labor Union Women. Women care about health care, 1993; Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Women Care about Health Care, Publication (Box 34, Folder 24)
    By Coalition of Labor Union Women. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Coast Committee for the Shipowners. A.B.C.'s of the maritime strike: a primer of basic facts, hiring halls, ship subsidy, arbitration awards, enforcement, 1936; Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: A.B.C.'s of the Maritime Strike, Publication (Box 34, Folder 25)
    By The Coast Committee for Shipowners. December 3, 1936 - Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Cogen for President Committee. First Cogen progressive administration: 196u, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The First Cogen Progressive Administration, Publication (Box 34, Folder 26)
    By Cogen for President Committee. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Cogen for President Committee. What Charles Cogen believes in 196u, Publication (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: What Charles Cogen Believes In, Publication (Box 34, Folder 27)
    By Cogen for President Committee. Item is in English.
- El Comite - Movimiento de Izquierda Nacional Puerto riquexo. Process of Puerto Rican migration and the U.S. working class, 1975; Publication (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Process of Puerto Rican Migration and the U.S. Working Class, Publication (Box 34, Folder 28)
    By El Comite. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Committee for Economic Development. Postwar employment and the settlement of terminated war contracts: a statement on National policy by Research Committee of the Committee for Economic Development, 1944; Publication (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Postwar employment and the settlement of terminated war contracts, Publication (Box 34, Folder 29)
    By Committee for Economic Development. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Community Labor Party. UAW faces the 80's/by General Baker, Jr., 1980; Publication (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The UAW Faces the 80's, Publication (Box 34, Folder 30)
    By General Baker, Jr. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Communist Labor Party. Victory to Jesse Jackson, victory to the working class / by the Communist Labor Party, 1988; Publication (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Victory to Jesse Jackson Victory to the Working Class, Publication (Box 34, Folder 31)
    By Communist Labor Party. May 1988. Item is in English.
- Communist Labor Party of the United States of North America. Fight for jobs: Communist Labor Party of the United States of North America (C.L.P.U.S.N.A.), 1975; Publication (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Fight for Jobs, Publication (Box 34, Folder 32)
    By Communist Labor Party of the United States of North America. September 1975. Item is in English.
- Communist Party of California. Let's get off the dime / by Frank Carlson: 194u, Publication (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Let's Get Off The Dime, Publication (Box 34, Folder 33)
    By Frank Carlson. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Communist Party of Massachusetts. Jobs, security, democracy and peace, 1938; Publication (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Jobs Security Democracy and Peace, Publication (Box 34, Folder 34)
    By Communist Party of Massachusetts. June 1938. Item is in English.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Can everybody be rich and still be honest? / Jim West, 1951; Publication (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Can Everybody Be Rich and Still be Honest?, Publication (Box 34, Folder 35)
    By Jim West. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Capitalism defends itself through the Socialist Labor Party: an expose of what stands behind the S.L.P. attack on Comrade William Z. Foster / by Moissaye J. Olgin, 1932; Publication (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Capitalism Defends Itself Through the Socialist Labor Party, Publication (Box 34, Folder 36)
    By M.J. Olgin. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. For a powerful United A.F. of L., 1936; Publication (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: For a Powerful United A.F. of L., Publication (Box 34, Folder 37)
    By Communist Party of the U.S.A. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Resumen del proyecto de programa del Partido Comunista de Los Estados Unidos y Commentarios: una programa para todos el pueblo / por Felix Ojeda, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Un programa para todo el Pueblo, Publication (Box 34, Folder 38)
    By Communist Party of the U.S.A. Pamphlet. Item is in Spanish.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Short History of Chicago Workers, Publication (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Short History of Chicano Workers, Publication (Box 34, Folder 39)
    By Lorenzo Torrez. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Working class against capitalist class is the main election issue of the Communist Party, 1930; Publication (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Working Class against Capalist Class, Publication (Box 34, Folder 40)
    By Communist Party of the U.S.A. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Central Committee. American Working Women and the class struggle 193u, Publication (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: American Working Women and the Class Struggle, Publication (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Communist Party, U.S.A. Steel and Metal Workers Commission. Shake-out in steel / by Rick nagin, 1978; Publication (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Shake-Out in Steel, Publication (Box 34, Folder 42)
    By Rick Nagin. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Conference for Progressive Labor Action. CPLA program, policies, 1933; Publication (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: CPLA Program Policies, Publication (Box 34, Folder 43)
    By Conference for Progressive Labor Action. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Conference for Progressive Labor Action. Marion murder: the story of the tragic day of October 2, 1929: funeral addresses / by Francis J. Gorman, Tom Tippett, A.J. Muste, Publication (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: The Marion Murder, Publication (Box 34, Folder 44)
    By Conference for Progressive Labor Action. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Conservative Society of America. Labor's International Network / by Hilaire du Berrier, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Labor's International Network, Publication (Box 34, Folder 45)
    By Hiliaire du Berrier. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Consumers' League of Ohio. Mr. Davey, minimum wage and the Civil Service, 1936; Publication (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Mr. Dave, minimum Wage and the Civil Service, Publication (Box 34, Folder 46)
    By Consumers' League of Ohio. Pmaphlet. Item is in English.
- The Co-Operative League of the USA. Labor and Co-ops / by James Myers, 1943; Publication (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Labor and Co-Ops, Publication (Box 34, Folder 47)
    By James Myers. Pmaphlet 1940. Item is in English.
- Cornell University. ILR School. New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Proudly honors Lois S. Gray: founder and former Dean-Extension Division. Jean McKelvey-Alice Grant Professor of Labor-Management Relations, Celebrating 50 years, 1996, Publication (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Celebrating 50 Years, Publication (Box 34, Folder 48)
    By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Booklet - Booklet - March 27, 1996. Item is in English.
- Correspondence Publishing Co. Union Committeemen and Wildcat Strikes / Martin Glaberman, 1955; Publication (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Union Committeemen and Wildcat Strikes, Publication (Box 34, Folder 49)
    By Correspondence Publishing Co. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Curtiss-Wright Corporation. Propeller Division. Factory rules, 1943; Publication (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Factory Rules, Publication (Box 34, Folder 50)
    By Curtiss-Wright Corporation. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Democratic National Committee (U.S.) Women's Division. Organizing for Democratic victory: a hardbook for county precinct leaders, 1946; Publication (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Organizing for Democratic Victory, Publication (Box 34, Folder 51)
    By Women's Division - Democratic National Committee. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Detroit Marxist-Leninist Organization. Why white workers should support affirmative action / by the Detroit Marxist Leninist Organization, 1979; Publication (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Why White Workers Should support Affirmative Action, Publication (Box 34, Folder 52)
    By Detroit Marxist-Leninist Organization. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Electrical Industry - Joint Industry Board. Pension Committee. Annuity plan of the Electrical industry: vested interest, monthly payments, retirement benefits, beneficiary benefits, death benefits, dividends, 1974; Publication (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Anuuity Plan of the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 34, Folder 53)
    By Electrical Industry. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Electrical Industry: Joint Industry Board: Pension Committee. Pension, hospitalization benefit plan of the Electrical industry: pensions, major medical, hospitalization, surgery, death of pension premium, serious injury, rest home, dental, medical, loans, 1971; Publication (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Pension, Hospitalization Benefit Plan of the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 34, Folder 54)
    By Electrical Industry - Joint Industry Board. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Electrical Industry: Joint Industry Board. Plan Committee. Additional security benefits plan of the electrical industry: unemployment benefit, compensation benefit, disability benefit, vacation benefit, death benefit, economic assistance, 1974; Publication (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Addistional Security Benefits Plan of the Electrical Industry, Publication (Box 34, Folder 55)
- Friends of the Soviet Union. Through workers' eyes: report of the American Workers Delegation to Russia [1931?], Publication (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Through Workers Eyes, Publication (Box 34, Folder 56)
    By Friends of the Secret Union. Booklet. Item is in English.
- General Electric Company. Compulsory unionism: a report to management, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 34, Folder 57)
    By General Electric Company. Relations News Letter. Item is in English.
- General Electric Company. Let's look at: the record of some strikes in General Electric: how much they cost employees: how they came out: what some employees thought, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: The Record of Some Strikes in General Electric, Publication (Box 34, Folder 58)
    By General Electric Company. Item is in English.
- Hendrick Smith Productions. Juggling work and family: with Hendrick Smith: viewer/discussion leader guide n.d., Publication (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Juggling Work and Family, Publication (Box 34, Folder 59)
    By Hendrick Smith Productions. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Highlander Folk School. Education unlimited: a handbook on union education in the South/written by Mary Lawrence, 1945; Publication (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Education Unlimited, Publication (Box 34, Folder 60)
    By Mary Lawrence. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Illinois Department of Transportation. Personnel policies manual: appendix 1 to Departmental Order 3-1-1995, Publication (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policies Manual, Publication (Box 34, Folder 61)
    By Illinois Department of Transportation. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Independent Labor League of America. Draft program of action, 1938; Publication (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Program of Action, Publication (Box 34, Folder 62)
    By Independent Labor League of America. Item is in English.
- Independent Socialist Committee. Toward the working class: a position paper for the New Left / by Kim Moody, Fred Eppsteiner, Mike Plug: together with Why the working class? / by Hal Draper, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Toward the working class, Publication (Box 34, Folder 63)
    By Hal Draper. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- International Labor Defense - Scottsboro, Publication (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Scottsboro, Publication (Box 34, Folder 64)
    By Sasha Small. Item is in English.
- The International Labor Defense. Under arrest!: Workers' self-defense in the courts / issued by the International Labor Defense, Publication (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Under Arrest!, Publication (Box 34, Folder 65)
    By International Labor Defense. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- International Labor Defense. Chicago District. Charge - rioting, verdict: not guilty!: a plea to a jury / by Albert Goldman, 1932; Publication (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Charge: Rioting Verdict: Not Guilty!, Publication (Box 34, Folder 66)
    By Albert Goldman. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- International Workers Order. National Executive Committee. New workers' strong hold: what is the International Workers' Order and why every worker should join it, 1930; Publication (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: A New Workers' Stronghold, Publication (Box 34, Folder 67)
    By National Executive Committee, International Workers' Order. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Int'l. Labor Defense. Northern Calif. - The C.S. Case Against, Publication (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: The C.S. Case Agaisnt Labor, Publication (Box 34, Folder 68)
    By International Labor Defense - Northern California District. Item is in English.
- Joint Marine Modesto Defense Committee. Modesto frame-up, 1935; Publication (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: The C.S. Case Against Labor, Publication (Box 34, Folder 69)
    By International Labor Defense - Northern California District. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Kansas. Kansas Court of Industrial Relation: (substitute for Senate Bill no.1) an act creating the Court of Industrial Relations, defining its powers and duties, and relating thereto, abolishing the Public Utilities Commission, repealing all acts and part, 1920; Publication (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: The Modesto Frame-Up, Publication (Box 34, Folder 70)
    By Joint Marine Modesto Defense Committee. Item is in English.
- Kentucky Miners Defense - Bloody Harlan. The Story of Four Miners, Publication (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Kansas Laws, Statues, etc., Publication (Box 34, Folder 71)
    By Kansas Court of Industrial Relations. Item is in English.
- King - Ramsey - Conner Defense: Not Guilty!, Publication (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Bloddy Harlan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 72)
    By Kentucky Miners Defense. Item is in English.
- Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace. Labor voice for peace, 1968; Publication (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: The ship Murder Frame-Up, Publication (Box 34, Folder 73)
    By King-Ramsay-Conner Defense. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Labor League for Thomas B. Nelson. What Roosevelt did for us, 1936; Publication (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Labor Voice for Peace, Publication (Box 34, Folder 74)
    By Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace. January 1968 - Newspaper. Item is in English.
- Labor-Negro Vanguard Conference. Model plan for the total integration of Negroes into American life / by Clarence Coggins, 1946; Publication (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: What Roosevelt Did For Us, Publication (Box 34, Folder 75)
    By Labor League for Thomas & Nelson. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Labor Party Association. America for the people!: why we need a farmer labor party / by Ben Gitlow, 1933; Publication (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Model Plan for the Total Integration of Negroes into American Life, Publication (Box 34, Folder 76)
    By Clarence Coggins. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Labor Youth League. Labor movement and the youth / prepared by the National Sub-Committee on industrial work of the L.Y.L., 1954; Publication (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: America for the People!, Publication (Box 34, Folder 77)
    By Ben Gitlow. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- The League Machine Tool Co. Scanlon Plan: (Plant-wide Incentive Bonus Plan), Hudson, Mass. 195u, Publication (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: The Labor Movement and the Youth, Publication (Box 34, Folder 78)
    By Labor Youth League. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- League for Independent Political Action. Unemployment: a practical program / by Henry Raymond Mussey, 1930; Publication (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Scanlon Plan, Publication (Box 34, Folder 79)
    By The Lapointe Machine Tool Co. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. British labor as government and as opposition / by Harry W. Laidler, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Unemployment - A Practical Program, Publication (Box 34, Folder 80)
    By Henry Raymond Mussey. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. Forty years of education: the task ahead / Symposium edited by Harry W. Laidler, 1945; Publication (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: British Labor as Government and as Opposition, Publication (Box 34, Folder 81)
    By Harry W. Laidler. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. How America lives: a handbook of industrial facts / by Harry W. Laidler, 1924; Publication (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: 40 Years of Education, Publication (Box 34, Folder 82)
    By League for Industrial Democracy. Booklet. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. How America lives: a handbook of industrial facts / by Harry W. Laidler, 1930; Publication (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: How America Lives, Publication (Box 34, Folder 83)
    By Harry W. Laidler. Booklet. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. Intellectual and the labor movement / by Georg Soule, 1923; Publication (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: How America Lives, Publication (Box 34, Folder 84)
    By Henry W. Laidler. Booklet. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. Labor governments at work; British, Scandinavian, Australian, 1948; Publication (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: The Intellectual and The Labor Movement, Publication (Box 34, Folder 85)
    By Geroge Soule. Booklet. Item is in English.
- League for Industrial Democracy. What is industrial democracy? By Norman Thomas, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Labor Governments at Work, Publication (Box 34, Folder 86)
- Massachusetts Trade Union Educational League. Current State of the U.S. labor movement / by Don Tomey: with introductory remarks by Rich Kontzand with questions, answers, and discussion, 1979; Publication (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: What is Industrial Democracy?, Publication (Box 34, Folder 87)
    By Norman Thomas. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Massachusetts Trade Union Educational League. Organized labor faces the 1980's / by Wilbur Hobby, Publication (Box 34, Folder 88)